I think this plan is feasible.
أعتقد أن هذه الخطة ممكنة.
Take a look.
إلق نظرة.
Okay, I got it.
حسنا حصلت عليه.
President Chen.
الرئيس تشين.
Everyone is here.
الكل هنا.
President Chen is here.
الرئيس تشين هنا.
In that case,
في هذه الحالة،
Then let's start.
ثم لنبدأ.
It seems that Mr. Long has a problem
يبدو أن السيد لونج لديه مشكلة
I'm very interested.
انا مهتم جدا.
Came to work in person.
جاء للعمل شخصيا.
Leader Liu.
الزعيم ليو.
Let's start.
لنبدأ.
Here's the thing, Team Leader Liu.
هذا هو الشيء ، قائد الفريق ليو.
Don't worry about President Long.
لا تقلق بشأن الرئيس لونج.
Although he doesn't come to work very often,
على الرغم من أنه لا يأتي للعمل كثيرًا ،
but
لكن
He can definitely keep up with the progress.
يمكنه بالتأكيد مواكبة التقدم.
Yes
نعم
this
هذه
President Chen, in some ways,
الرئيس تشين ، من بعض النواحي ،
Can still represent me.
لا يزال يمكن أن يمثلني.
Let's start.
لنبدأ.
Mr. Long, President Chen.
السيد لونغ ، الرئيس تشين.
The direction of Long Mei Island's game plan.
اتجاه خطة لعبة Long Mei Island.
Long Mei Island.
جزيرة لونغ مي.
There are a few.
هناك عدد قليل.
Chen Xuanyi
تشن شواني
Long Mei Island is my personal property.
جزيرة لونغ مي هي ممتلكاتي الشخصية.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Really?
هل حقا؟
You have to ask.
عليك أن تسأل.
Uncle Long and Aunt Yang
العم لونغ والعمّة يانغ
They gave me the access.
لقد أعطوني الوصول.
Leader Liu, continue.
القائد ليو ، تابع.
Okay, I will continue.
حسنًا ، سأستمر.
wife
زوجة
How are you, honey?
كيف حالك يا عزيزي؟
Chen Xuan Yi
تشن شوان يي
I'm telling you,
أنا أخبرك،
I didn't want to go to the company.
لم أرغب في الذهاب إلى الشركة.
You insist on fixing the Omey box.
أنت تصر على إصلاح صندوق Omey.
I told you.
أخبرتك.
Yes
نعم
And gave our Long Mei Island
وأعطينا جزيرة لونغ مي
Honey, what's wrong with you?
عزيزتي ، ما خطبك؟
tired
مرهق
It's all my fault.
هذا كله خطأي.
I will pick you up from now on.
سأقلك من الآن فصاعدا.
No need
لا حاجة
Then drive yourself.
ثم قم بالقيادة بنفسك.
I'm lazy.
أنا كسول.
Yes
نعم
My wife is having an interview today.
زوجتي تجري مقابلة اليوم.
I don't know which lucky one.
لا أعرف أيهما محظوظ.
Won the favor of my wife.
فازت لصالح زوجتي.
I don't want to talk.
لا اريد التحدث.
If you don't want to talk, you can't.
إذا كنت لا تريد التحدث ، فلا يمكنك ذلك.
The imperial sedan.
السيارة الامبراطورية.
go
يذهب
Let's go.
لنذهب.
husband
الزوج
Why don't you blow on your hair?
لماذا لا تنفخ على شعرك؟
The hair is hanging here.
الشعر معلق هنا.
You will get a headache.
سوف تصاب بصداع.
Haven't I told you?
ألم أخبرك؟
husband
الزوج
Did I get married early?
هل تزوجت مبكرا؟
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
I said,
انا قلت،
It's great to marry you.
إنه لشيء رائع أن أتزوجك.
wife
زوجة
I might come up with a difference.
قد أتوصل إلى اختلاف.
I can't see you for another week.
لا أستطيع رؤيتك لأسبوع آخر.
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
Chen Xuanyi asked me to go to Long Mei Island with her.
طلب مني Chen Xuanyi أن أذهب معها إلى جزيرة Long Mei.
What company? Get a broken box.
ما الشركة؟  احصل على صندوق مكسور.
wife
زوجة
to feel relieved
ليشعروا بالارتياح
It's just work.
إنه عمل فقط.
work
الشغل
I'm not going.
أنا لن أذهب.
Go to the interview with my wife.
اذهب إلى المقابلة مع زوجتي.
No way
مستحيل
Work is important, of course.
العمل مهم بالطبع.
Why are you with me?
لماذا انت معي
wife
زوجة
In fact, sometimes work is a kind of fate.
في الواقع ، أحيانًا يكون العمل نوعًا من القدر.
There's no need to be anxious.
لا داعي للقلق.
Sometimes, for a change,
في بعض الأحيان ، من أجل التغيير ،
There will be unexpected gains.
ستكون هناك مكاسب غير متوقعة.
Don't be nervous.
لا تكن عصبيا.
Good morning.
صباح الخير.
Dude,
يا صاحبي،
I can't be with you today.
لا استطيع ان اكون معك اليوم.
I have serious business.
لدي عمل جاد.
He will go too.
سوف يذهب أيضا.
Please introduce him.
الرجاء تقديمه.
This is President Long Chen Ji.
هذا هو الرئيس لونغ تشن جي.
The owner of Long Mei Island.
صاحب جزيرة Long Mei.
This is Master Kitano.
هذا هو ماستر كيتانو.
The chief designer of Long Mei Island.
المصمم الرئيسي لجزيرة Long Mei.
Master Kitano.
سيد كيتانو.
You have many titles.
لديك ألقاب كثيرة.
It's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
what?
ماذا؟
You're willing to work today.
أنت على استعداد للعمل اليوم.
You are waiting for me to carry your luggage.
أنت تنتظر مني أن أحمل أمتعتك.
Help me carry the luggage.
ساعدني في حمل الأمتعة.
I'm a guest.
انا ضيف.
you
أنت
Sometimes, for a change,
في بعض الأحيان ، من أجل التغيير ،
There will be unexpected gains.
ستكون هناك مكاسب غير متوقعة.
Don't be nervous.
لا تكن عصبيا.
Alright. Let's change.
على ما يرام.  دعونا نتغير.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Director Wang.
المخرج وانغ.
Hello, Director Wang.
مرحبا المخرج وانغ.
I'm Zhang Yiyi.
أنا تشانغ ييي.
This is my resume.
هذه سيرتي الذاتية.
Zhang Yiyi.
تشانغ ييي.
New guy, right?
شاب جديد ، أليس كذلك؟
What about
ماذا عن
I have some experience.
لدي بعض الخبرة.
Give it a try.
جربها.
Okay, let's try.
حسنًا ، دعنا نحاول.
Thank you, Director Wang.
شكرا لك المخرج وانغ.
Long Yi.
لونغ يي.
Are you sure you want to leave Zhang Jingmei?
هل أنت متأكد أنك تريد مغادرة Zhang Jingmei؟
Are you going to Long Mei Island alone?
أنت ذاهب إلى جزيرة لونغ مي وحدك؟
Aren't you afraid that Zhang Jingmei will find out?
ألا تخشى أن يكتشف تشانغ جينغمي ذلك؟
I won't forgive you.
لن أسامحك.
Why don't you find another chance?
لماذا لا تجد فرصة أخرى؟
Let's go together.
لنذهب معا.
You're afraid of me.
أنت خائف مني.
To interfere with your relationship with Chen Xuanyi, right?
للتدخل في علاقتك مع Chen Xuanyi ، أليس كذلك؟
Be quiet.
كن هادئاً.
I'm serious this time.
أنا جاد هذه المرة.
Seriously.
بشكل جاد.
I'm warning you.
أنا أحذرك.
If you dare to treat Chen Xuan Yi badly,
إذا كنت تجرؤ على معاملة Chen Xuan Yi بشكل سيء ،
I won't let you off first.
لن أتركك أولاً.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Don't you want to take your luggage?
ألا تريد أن تأخذ أمتعتك؟
He's here.
إنه هنا.
shoot!
أطلق النار!
I forgot to call.
لقد نسيت الاتصال.
wife
زوجة
I'm at the airport.
أنا في المطار.
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
I
أنا
Jialin and I are drinking milk tea.
أنا وجيالين نشرب الشاي بالحليب.
And drink milk tea.
وشرب الشاي بالحليب.
Okay, bye.
حسنًا ، إلى اللقاء.
I haven't finished yet.
لم أنتهي بعد.
Leave.
غادر.
Long Yi, where are you going?
لونغ يي ، إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Let's go, Xuan Yi.
دعنا نذهب ، شوان يي.
I'm always here.
أنا دائما هنا.
Don't worry about him.
لا تقلق عليه.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Long Yi is
لونغ يي
Is only reliable for one person.
يمكن الاعتماد عليها فقط لشخص واحد.
President Chen.
الرئيس تشين.
The check-in is done.
تم تسجيل الوصول.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Okay, let's go.
حسنا دعنا نذهب.
He will go too.
سوف يذهب أيضا.
Get out of the car.
أخرج من السيارة.
Jingmei
جينغمي
Thank you so much this time.
شكرا جزيلا لك هذه المرة.
To give them such a good chance.
لمنحهم مثل هذه الفرصة الجيدة.
We also provide a training ground.
نحن نوفر أيضًا ساحة تدريب.
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
I should thank you, okay?
يجب أن أشكرك ، حسنًا؟
The cast needs people urgently.
فريق التمثيل يحتاج الناس بشكل عاجل.
Only you.
أنت فقط.
So I can give you the code.
لذا يمكنني أن أعطيك الرمز.
You're a close friend.
أنت صديق مقرب.
Come on, brothers.
تعال يا إخوتي.
Everyone knows the plot.
الكل يعرف المؤامرة.
Time is limited.
الوقت محدود.
Everyone, hurry up and practice.
الجميع ، أسرعوا وتدربوا.
Alright, sis.
حَسَنًا ، أَخْتَى.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
no problem
لا مشكلة
The milk tea is too much.
شاي الحليب كثير جدا.
It's perfect.
انها مثالية.
Open the door.
افتح الباب.
Open the door?
افتح الباب؟
This is a private place.
هذا مكان خاص.
Don't make trouble.
لا تجعل المتاعب.
Leave now.
ارحل الآن.
I know this is a private place.
أعلم أن هذا مكان خاص.
I'm Long Yi.
أنا لونغ يي.
I want you to open the door.
أريدك أن تفتح الباب.
Don't you understand?
الا تفهم
What happened to Long Yi?
ماذا حدث لـ Long Yi؟
I'm officially warning you.
أنا أحذرك رسميًا.
If you don't leave,
إذا لم ترحل ،
I'll call the police.
سأتصل بالشرطة.
go
يذهب
You're very dutiful.
أنت مطيع جدا.
You want to change your job?
تريد تغيير عملك؟
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
He kept knocking on the door.
ظل يطرق الباب.
We can't let him in.
لا يمكننا السماح له بالدخول.
Young Master Long.
السيد الشاب لونج.
What Young Master Long?
ما سيد الشاب طويل؟
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Young Master Long.
السيد الشاب لونج.
This is Young Master Long.
هذا السيد الشاب لونج.
He didn't know it was you.
لم يكن يعلم أنه أنت.
Young Master Long, I've never seen you before.
السيد الشاب لونج ، لم أرك من قبل.
Young Master Long.
السيد الشاب لونج.
Zhang Jingmei
تشانغ جينغمي
Young Master Long, take it easy.
السيد الشاب لونج ، خذ الأمور ببساطة.
Young Master Long.
السيد الشاب لونج.
I'm really sorry, Young Master Long.
أنا آسف حقًا ، السيد الصغير لونج.
I didn't blame you.
أنا لم ألومك.
Young Master Long, Young
السيد الشاب لونغ ، يونغ
He's new here.
إنه جديد هنا.
Don't blame him.
لا تلوموه.
Don't fire him.
لا تطرده.
Give him another chance.
أعطه فرصة أخرى.
At ease, at attention.
براحة ، منتبهة.
For two hours.
لساعتين.
yes
نعم
Young Master Long, please wait.
السيد الشاب لونج ، من فضلك انتظر.
Open mine.
افتحه لي.
hello
أهلا
Welcome to Long Mei Island.
مرحبًا بكم في جزيرة Long Mei.
The environment is good.
البيئة جيدة.
Let's take a rest today.
لنأخذ قسطا من الراحة اليوم.
We'll start work tomorrow.
سنبدأ العمل غدا.
President Chen.
الرئيس تشين.
We have three rooms for you.
لدينا ثلاث غرف لك.
One room on the third floor.
غرفة واحدة في الطابق الثالث.
There are two rooms on the second floor.
هناك غرفتان في الطابق الثاني.
I don't know who lives on the third floor.
لا أعرف من يعيش في الطابق الثالث.
The third floor has a nice view.
الطابق الثالث له منظر جميل.
With a broad vision.
برؤية واسعة.
Luo is always a guest.
لوه دائما ضيف.
Why don't you stay on the third floor?
لماذا لا تبقى في الطابق الثالث؟
The scenery on the second floor is equally good and open.
المشهد في الطابق الثاني جيد ومفتوح بنفس القدر.
Right?
حق؟
You both live on the second floor.
كلاكما تعيشان في الطابق الثاني.
I live on the third floor.
أنا أعيش في الطابق الثالث.
Slow down.
ابطئ.
What?
ماذا؟
I'll leave them to you.
سأتركهم لك.
Take care of it for me.
اعتني بها من اجلي
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Get back to work.
عد الى العمل.
You kept it from me.
لقد احتفظت بها عني.
Yiyi.
ييي.
Yiyi, you're back.
Yiyi ، لقد عدت.
The director is looking for you.
المدير يبحث عنك.
Then let's go.
إذا دعنا نذهب.
Yiyi.
ييي.
Come on.
هيا.
Everyone, come with me.
الجميع ، تعالوا معي.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Stay close behind.
ابق على مقربة من الخلف.
to do sth more quickly
للقيام بالكثير بسرعة أكبر
Mr. Luo,
السيد لو ،
Are you busy?
هل أنت مشغول؟
You know,
أنت تعرف،
Everything is good on Long Mei Island.
كل شيء جيد في جزيرة Long Mei.
But it's the same.
لكنها نفس الشيء.
There are too few people.
هناك عدد قليل جدا من الناس.
Isn't this a private island?
أليست هذه جزيرة خاصة؟
Has not been developed into a commercial island.
لم يتم تطويره إلى جزيرة تجارية.
So,
لذا،
You know,
أنت تعرف،
President Chen, as a girl,
الرئيس تشين ، كفتاة ،
Let her live on the third floor alone.
دعها تعيش في الطابق الثالث وحدها.
Is it too dangerous?
هل هو خطير جدا؟
If something happens,
إذا حدث شيء ما ،
We don't know.
لا نعلم.
Mr. Luo,
السيد لو ،
Be frank with me.
كن صريحا معي.
Your room
غرفتك
Nice environment.
بيئة جميلة.
The lighting is good.
الإضاءة جيدة.
It's good.
إنه جيد.
Alright, Mr. Luo.
حسنًا ، سيد لو.
I'll do it now.
سأفعل ذلك الآن.
You're really an excellent assistant.
أنت حقًا مساعد ممتاز.
sister
أخت
These are the two artists my sister brought.
هذان هما الفنانان اللذان أحضرتهما أختي.
You have a good image.
لديك صورة جيدة.
She has a good image.
لديها صورة جيدة.
Smile.
يبتسم.
Sign it later.
وقع عليه لاحقًا.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Then, Sister Busy,
ثم ، الأخت مشغولة ،
Zhang Yiyi.
تشانغ ييي.
Stand there.
قف هناك.
I'll stand on a hammer.
سأقف على مطرقة.
line up
اصطفوا
Then it's hard.
ثم من الصعب.
Take care of these two newbies.
اعتني بهذين المبتدئين.
Come on.
هيا.
Everyone, please sign your names.
الجميع ، الرجاء التوقيع على الأسماء الخاصة بك.
Pass them on.
انقلهم.
Everyone is here.
الكل هنا.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Take care of him.
الاعتناء به.
Okay, don't worry.
حسنًا ، لا تقلق.
to
إلى
autograph
توقيعه
What are you writing?
ماذا تكتب؟
You think you're the best?
هل تعتقد أنك الأفضل؟
How will I pay you later?
كيف سأدفع لك لاحقا؟
What payment?
ما الدفع؟
Look at the clear script.
انظر إلى النص الواضح.
Pay by name.
ادفع بالاسم.
You wrote this?
انت كتبت هذا؟
I'll jump there.
سأقفز هناك.
Change it.
غيره.
to wait a moment
انتظر لحظة
I just came here.
لقد جئت للتو إلى هنا.
He's handsome.
انه وسيم.
The styling is not good.
التصميم ليس جيدًا.
To cover your face.
لتغطية وجهك.
Change your style next time.
غير طريقتك في المرة القادمة.
Correct!
صحيح!
When he dies later,
عندما مات لاحقا ،
Remember to face up.
تذكر أن تواجه.
Stay closer to the main character.
ابق أقرب إلى الشخصية الرئيسية.
You will die later.
سوف تموت لاحقا.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Look at those two.
انظر إلى هذين.
One is a group leader.
واحد هو قائد المجموعة.
One is an actor and assistant director.
واحد هو ممثل ومساعد مخرج.
If you want to live well,
إذا كنت تريد أن تعيش بشكل جيد ،
We have to get close to them first.
علينا أن نقترب منهم أولاً.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Then the person whose name I called
ثم الشخص الذي اتصلت باسمه
Can you answer me?
يمكنك الإجابة لي؟
Sun Jingming.
صن جينغ مينغ.
reach
تصل
Jia Xiaoqiang
جيا شياو تشيانغ
WangZhi
WangZhi
reach
تصل
Song Guangwei
سونغ قوانغ وى
Long Er.
طويل.
Who is Long Er?
من هو Long Er؟
No,
رقم،
There's no such two names.
لا يوجد مثل هذين الاسمين.
I
أنا
I'm Long Er.
أنا Long Er.
Hello, Deputy Director Zhang Yi.
مرحبًا ، نائب المدير تشانغ يي.
Please give me more advice.
من فضلك أعطني المزيد من النصائح.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Long Er.
طويل.
Didn't you go to Long Mei Island?
ألم تذهب إلى جزيرة لونغ مي؟
Zhang Yiyi.
تشانغ ييي.
Your milk tea is very nourishing this morning.
شاي الحليب الخاص بك مغذي للغاية هذا الصباح.
You followed me?
هل اتبعتني؟
joke
نكتة
My Dragon Master
سيد التنين الخاص بي
Will follow you.
سوف أتبعك.
I followed my wife.
لقد تابعت زوجتي.
Zhang Jingmei
تشانغ جينغمي
Okay, it's my fault.
حسنًا ، هذا خطأي.
I shouldn't have kept it from you.
ما كان يجب أن أمنعها عنك.
But I have my reasons.
لكن لدي أسبابي.
What difficulties?
ما الصعوبات؟
Zhang Jingmei is Mrs. Long.
تشانغ جينغمي هي السيدة لونج.
This identity is too famous.
هذه الهوية مشهورة جدًا.
The crew didn't dare to use me.
لم يجرؤ الطاقم على استخدامي.
Who dares to use it?
من يجرؤ على استخدامه؟
Look, look.
انظر انظر.
Because of you.
بسببك.
They dare not use mine.
يجرؤون على عدم استخدام المنجم.
Then why do you have to let them use it?
إذن لماذا يجب أن تسمح لهم باستخدامه؟
Yiyi.
ييي.
The director is looking for you.
المدير يبحث عنك.
good
جيد
I'll be there soon.
سأكون هناك قريبا.
All right, I have to get back to work.
حسنًا ، يجب أن أعود إلى العمل.
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
Go back now.
ارجع الآن.
Let's go home tonight.
لنذهب للمنزل الليلة.
I'm not going back.
لن أعود.
Then what are you doing?
ثم ماذا تفعل؟
I'm acting.
أنا أمثل.
You...
أنت...
What happened to me
ماذا حدث لي
See that?
أنظر لهذا؟
You passed the interview.
لقد اجتزت المقابلة.
Oops.
أُووبس.
Stop it, Young Master Long.
توقف عن ذلك ، السيد الشاب لونج.
sorry
آسف
I
أنا
Is an actor.
غير فاعل.
Mr. Luo, it's been a long time.
السيد لو ، لقد مر وقت طويل.
Please sit down.
من فضلك اجلس.
We are so close.
نحن قريبون جدا.
I still like to hear you calling me.
ما زلت أحب أن أسمعك تناديني.
Beichen
بيتشين
Mr.Luo
السيد لو
I heard you're thoughtful for me.
سمعت أنك تفكر بالنسبة لي.
You even changed rooms with me.
حتى أنك غيرت الغرف معي.
It's proper to protect the beauty.
من المناسب حماية الجمال.
Moreover,
علاوة على ذلك،
To protect you.
لحمايتك.
I won't be so hard on you.
لن أكون صعبًا عليك.
But I have to warn you.
لكن علي أن أحذرك.
What about the third floor?
ماذا عن الطابق الثالث؟
Is slightly smaller than the second floor.
أصغر بقليل من الطابق الثاني.
I hope you don't mind.
انا آمل انك لا تمانع.
Don't mind.
لا مانع.
No
رقم
What do I care?
لماذا أهتم؟
Ming Zhe has sent the luggage
أرسل مينغ زهي الأمتعة
To your room.
إلى غرفتك.
This is your room card.
هذه بطاقة غرفتك.
I changed rooms with you.
لقد غيرت الغرف معك.
Isn't it Zhao Mingzhe's room?
أليست غرفة Zhao Mingzhe؟
Ming Zhe will be here soon.
مينغ زهي سيكون هنا قريبا.
Brother Xu, calm down.
الأخ شو ، إهدأ.
The executive director is in a hurry.
المدير التنفيذي في عجلة من أمره.
To make a good film.
لعمل فيلم جيد.
Right?
حق؟
Shoot it.
اطلاق الرصاص عليه.
I didn't say I won't shoot.
لم أقل أنني لن أطلق النار.
Keep shooting.
الحفاظ على اطلاق النار.
Brother Xu.
الأخ شو.
to regret leaving
لتندم على المغادرة
Why don't you let Xu take a rest?
لماذا لا تدع (شو) يأخذ قسطا من الراحة؟
sister
أخت
It's been two hours.
لقد مرت ساعتان.
Look, I'm an actress.
اسمع ، أنا ممثلة.
Are lying on the ground waiting.
يرقدون على الأرض ينتظرون.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Zhang Jingmei
تشانغ جينغمي
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
You're not acting.
أنت لا تتصرف.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Didn't you see the strike?
ألم تشاهد الإضراب؟
Leave them alone.
دعهم و شأنهم.
Just mind our own business.
فقط اهتم بشؤوننا الخاصة.
No
رقم
What about Zhang Yiyi?
ماذا عن تشانغ ييي؟
This is what Yiyi is eating.
هذا ما يأكله يييي.
If you really want her best,
إذا كنت تريد حقًا أفضل ما لديها ،
Don't bother her.
لا تزعجها.
If you move around,
إذا تحركت ،
She will be scolded later.
سيتم توبيخها لاحقًا.
Namely
يسمى
No
رقم
Then you can look at it like this.
ثم يمكنك أن تنظر إليها هكذا.
A big man bullied her.
قام رجل كبير بتخويفها.
You can't say that.
لا يمكنك قول ذلك.
Everyone is doing their jobs.
الجميع يقومون بعملهم.
Work.
عمل.
What job?
أية وظيفة؟
What's the point?
ما هي النقطة؟
How many of you
كم منكم
I've been lying here all morning.
لقد كنت أستلقي هنا طوال الصباح.
Without a word.
بدون كلمة.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
Tell me what the point is.
قل لي ما هو الهدف.
Second Brother Long.
الأخ الثاني لونغ.
We have a camera.
لدينا كاميرا.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I played a corpse last time.
لقد لعبت دور الجثة آخر مرة.
But my mom
لكن أمي
Or did you see me on the camera?
أو هل رأيتني على الكاميرا؟
People should pursue their dreams when they are alive.
يجب على الناس متابعة أحلامهم عندما يكونون على قيد الحياة.
This is our dream.
هذا حلمنا.